[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diamond is the hardest known natural material on Earth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are aardvarks nocturnal animals?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company produces and distributes the citrus flavored soft drink Mello Yello?", "correct_answer": "Coca-Cola", "incorrect_answers": ["Pepsi", "Dr Pepper/Seven Up", "Cadbury-Schweppes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common name does the dog breed New Guinea Highland Dog have?", "correct_answer": "Singer", "incorrect_answers": ["Prowler", "Wrestler", "Swimmer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Discredited NFL referee Owen Templeton ends up driving a bus full of Mae West look-alikes in the movie Rat Race.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Epic Movie parody the movie Night at the Museum?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Arsenic and Old Lace, the whole story revolves around the evening of which celebration?", "correct_answer": "Halloween", "incorrect_answers": ["Easter", "Christmas", "St. Valentines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fastest time to eat this number of mince pies is 1 min : 52.67 seconds.", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["13", "21", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these species shed their skin. Which one does not?", "correct_answer": "Penguins", "incorrect_answers": ["Snakes", "Insects", "Crustaceans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of milk is the Grana Padano cheese made from?", "correct_answer": "Cows milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Sheeps milk", "Goats milk", "Buffalos milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In three of these movies James Bond drove an Aston Martin DB5. Can you spot the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Dr. No", "incorrect_answers": ["Goldfinger", "GoldenEye", "Thunderball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does chocolate affect blood cholesterol levels?", "correct_answer": "It raises only HDL (good cholesterol)", "incorrect_answers": ["It raises only LDL (bad cholesterol)", "It lowers only HDL (good cholesterol)", "It raises both LDL (bad cholesterol) and HDL(good cholesterol)"]}]